Способы связаться

zhiyenbayeva.z@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/zarina-panfilova-90947310a (LinkedIn)

Основные навыки

React JavaScript CSS

Languages

Русский (Native or Bilingual)
Английский (Professional Working)

Certifications

EFSET English Certificate - EF Score: 42/100, Intermediate (CEFR B1)

Responsive Web Design

Zarina Panfilova

Junior Software Engineer at EPAM Systems

Караганда, Карагандинская область, Казахстан

Общие сведения

I started my IT path as a Junior Software Testing Engineer.

After working in this role for 1 year, I moved to Systems Engineering.

I was working in the role of Support Engineer for 2.5 years.

As I was not the only person who was responsible for the support process in the project, I helped with additional activities that were critical for the project but usually out of the support scope.

I performed front-end tasks with pleasure, as I'm interested in front-end development.

I passed several online courses by myself and 2 mentorship courses. And finally I'm working in a role of Frontend Engineer.

My responsibilities were:

- Development of interfaces using JavaScript
- Project support (development, refactoring, bug fix, hot fix)
- Developing new components and maintaining existing code

Опыт работы

EPAM Systems
Junior Software Engineer
октября 2020 - Present (2 года 9 месяцев)
Каzakhstan

EPAM Systems

3 года 9 месяцев

System Engineer апреля 2019 - февраля 2020 (11 месяцев)

Kazakhstan

Junior System Engineer июня 2017 - марта 2019 (1 год 10 месяцев) Kazakhstan

Junior Software Testing Engineer

июня 2016 - мая 2017 (1 год)

Karaganda

Образование

КарГТУ

Бакалавр информатики, Информатика · (2013 - 2017)